How is it?
It's great!
Is anyone home?
Yes!
Coming...
Dai, long time no see.
Haruko!
What are you doing here?
Rin!
Reina?!
What's up, Reina?
Are you going somewhere?
Haruko...
Nope. We came to visit.
Oh?
Um...
Reina, do you like sweet buns?
What's that?
Round sweets.
Then I like it!
Rin, pour some barley tea for Reina.
Okay. Reina, let's go.
You came right during snack time!
I want snacks, too!
Bunny Drop
I dunno about tomorrow
It's different than a sacrifice Something's off
I don't think it's like some penalty game
So, why? I don't get it at all
I'm a little bit unsatisfied, but your presence
right now is more than just important
There's no such thing in this world
as something never-ending
Crying isn't painful, it's love's sweet drops, sweet drops!
I want to keep dreaming forever, ya know?
I want to be more kind, ya know?
As long as I'm with you, I'm happy
Girls sure are strong, ya know?
But sometimes we're weak, ya know?
Our wish is to be happy, happy, happy!
And those days will be happy, too!
Just wanna make you happy!
Yummy!
I know, right?
This is the first time I've had it!
Thank you.
Wow. I've never been here, but this place feels just like Grandpa's...
So what's wrong?
She has her schoolbag on a Sunday...
Oh, right...
The truth is...
we ran away from home.
You wh-wha...?!
Your in-laws will worry!
Why would you do that?!
Is it... uh... you know...?
Is it what?!
Y-You know. Your husband...
That's part of it.
Part of it?
Part of it!
And his parents...
That's a part of it too!
I-I guess it's difficult to live with your in-laws.
I wonder if it's even possible for a wife to live with in-laws in peace.
Whoa, scary!
I have no brothers or sisters and there's nowhere else for me to go.
That's the math book we use, too!
Can we stay here, Dai?
Really?
Let me see your other textbooks, too!
Let's talk things through first.
Sure. Um...
Now, what about your in-laws?
Your Japanese book is different from mine!
It's okay.
I left a note.
I wanna see yours!
I didn't say where we were going though...
Sure, let's go!
Only that I'd take Reina to school.
Other than that...
I didn't really think about it.
I haven't even told my parents yet...
"Didn't think"?
You have your daughter to consider.
You...
It's not like I had a choice!
I had to get out of that house!
I couldn't stand it another second!
Fine...
Let's go grocery shopping for tonight.
Dai...
I don't have much, but you can take the right room.
It really is different!
Thanks. It's a little heavy.
What the hell did you cram in here?!
Reina's slippers and textbooks are in there, too...
I'm surprised you made it this far.
Dai, you don't usually put much thought into meals, right?
Tonight, I'll cook you a real dinner.
I do think about it.
Daikichi, can we look at sweets?
You can each choose one thing.
Okay!
What kind of meat should we get?
It's all the same to me.
Not that one!
This one.
No, this one's a little...
Daikichi! Hello.
Dai, this ground beef and pork combo is really cheap...
Oh, crap!
Uh... This isn't what it looks like!
This is Haruko, my cousin from my mother's side!
Who cares what side I'm from?
O-Oh, really?
Nice to meet you!
My son is a classmate of Rin's. Daikichi is always helping me out...
What the hell am I saying?! She even didn't ask who it was!
Why did I feel the need to explain it to her?!
Oh? Then my daughter is the same age.
Oh, really?
"This isn't what it looks like"?! What the hell!
I'm Reina!
She's a first-grader this year, so...
I'm Kouki.
Oh, my!
Yo, Kouki!
What kind of sweets did you pick?
What's up, Daikichi!
This one!
Deluxe Big Nyan Gum!
I'm getting vegetable sponge cake!
I'm getting Meow Meow Kitty candy!
Are those really sweets?!
She's pretty, isn't she?
Y-Yeah, I suppose she's one of the more attractive moms...
But I don't think you should have an affair with her!
A-Are you out of your mind?!
It's not like that at all!
In the first place, she has enough trouble taking care of Kouki on her own!
She doesn't have the time to—
"On her own"?!
So during lunch at school...
Moron!
You watch too many weird dramas!
Uh-huh?
A bug got out of its cage!
I'm guessing she's two or three years older than us...
W-Why should I care how old she is?!
Really?!
So, is she divorced?
I don't know the details...
It looks delicious!
I haven't had this before!
I experimented a bit.
Usually, everything is made to my mother-in-law's tastes.
Mama, I wanna have this at home, too!
Well, let's eat.
Let's eat!
It's good!
Thank you, Rin!
Come on, Reina. Hold your chopsticks properly.
Okay!
The floor creaks!
Here, Reina, use this towel!
Okay!
What's that?
A bra!
Hey, Reina!
Don't pull on it like that!
Are they asleep?
Yeah, finally...
They were both pretty excited.
I moved Rin to your futon, Dai.
Thank you.
Thanks.
That hit the spot!
It's been so long since I've had alcohol.
Hungry?
I gain weight easily these days, so no thanks.
I'm not surprised...
Are you calling me fat?!
No, no, not at all.
It's just that we're in our thirties now.
I'm fine with being thirty...
You can't act the same as when you were younger, you know?
You've gotta be careful.
On the other hand, my husband doesn't even look at me anymore...
I don't even know why I try.
Haruko...
What?
While you were all taking a bath, I called your house.
Why?!
Don't do anything weird, Dai!
It's not weird.
You want everyone there to worry about you?!
All I said was that you two were fine and are going to stay here for a while.
I didn't even give my address.
I told you, I left a note so it's fine!
Leave me be!
It's not about you.
You can do what you want, but what about Reina?
Reina's with me and she's fine too, so there's no problem!
That may be, but if you don't tell them where you are and that Reina's okay,
how the hell are the people who are waiting gonna know?
I couldn't care less about them...
You need to be a little more level-headed about this.
Do you just wanna make trouble for your family?
Rin!
Come in here!
Sure.
That's my nose!
Papa and Mama are always fighting.
Even though they're married?
Yeah. Even though they're married. But I always pretend I'm sleeping...
Let's play!
Sure.
That tickles!
That's my cheek!
Every day, I... I...
Ever since I got married, I've had to hide how I felt!
I deserve this much, don't I?
Sorry, Dai.
I shouldn't have said those things.
It's okay...
I'm going to bed.
Dai...
Dai, good night.
Good night.
Rin...
Good morning!
Good morning...
Rin, are you making breakfast?
Uh-huh.
Daikichi, good morning!
You're up early today, huh?
Yeah, well...
Hey, Dai!
You have Rin make breakfast?!
W-What do you think I am?!
We always cook together!
And when we use the stove, I...
No fighting!
Look, you've got rice on your face.
Don't take too long to eat.
We're going to school by train today...
Rin!
What's going on? It's so early...
It's Kouki!
Yeah, all right!
Just come in!
You're disturbing the neighbors!
Is your school far, Rin?
You already have to leave?
Uh-uh.
Kouki's mom is busy, so he always comes over early.
G-Good morning.
Daikichi, did you get married?!
Of course not! She's my cousin!
Oh. I knew it was impossible.
What do you mean "I knew"?
Daikichi, do you wanna get married?
Look, I don't even know.
Mama, you like being single, right?
What's "single"?
It's not getting married.
I know that one! "Divorce", right?!
I don't know "divorce"!
Reina, your mom is married but single is better...
Daikichi, you're single, but is married better for you?
Adults really are weird, you know?
They are, aren't they?
Daikichi, can I have a rice ball?
You had breakfast before coming, didn't you?
Yeah.
Whatever. Go ahead.
It was mine though...
Score!
Didn't you already eat?
Why are you still hungry?
You're too nice for your own good, Dai.
What's the problem?
I ate it because I wanted to!
What, 'cause I gave him a rice ball?
Weirdo.
No, not that.
Then what?
You're just as busy as she is, right?
You really do have a thing for that beautiful mother...
St-Stu... Dumbass!
That again?!
I just thought I'd help her out a bit.
And Rin gets along with them too, so...
That's all.
I don't know the details,
but I'm pretty sure Kouki and his mother have been through a lot.
It would be rude of me to be too forward.
It must be hard, being a woman on her own...
Reina! I told you, hurry or you'll be late!
Mama always has just one piece of toast.
Haruko...
She says she's on a diet.
Good morning!
Good morning to you too.
Don't tell anyone we're staying with Daikichi.
Why?
Because I said so! Understand?
Okay!
Good morning!
Reina, did you come with your mother?
Yeah, that's right!
We secretly ran away from home, so I came by train today!
I don't get it!
Wait!
Hey!
Didn't I tell you to hold on tight?!
I'm not gonna get another one for you!
But maybe it'll get home before us!
That's right! Maybe it will!
Have a nice evening.
Huh? You're working late.
Yeah, my husband's watching him at home.
Oh. How's Yuu doing?
He's great!
He's so rambunctious these days. I can barely handle him!
But it's nice that your husband helps out.
This is the first time!
His business trip was suddenly rescheduled, so he had the day off.
Oh...
There's no way I can rely on my husband to raise our kid.
Hurry up! Let's go!
Reina's waiting!
Okay, okay...
We're home! Reina!
They fell asleep right away tonight.
Haruko, don't tell me...
You're not going to turn this into a big deal, are you?
Oh, you mean divorce or something?
Yeah, that.
No worries. That won't happen.
W-What the hell? I wasted time worrying about it.
Well, I have thought about it a number of times...
In fact, I think about it almost every day...
After all, I think of my husband as the enemy while living in his house.
Other than Reina, I feel like the whole house is against me.
I feel like the two of us make up the family.
But that isn't being very realistic, is it?
There's Reina... and whether I can support us...
And all the problems I'd have to face before I'd even reach that point.
At the end of the day, it looks like I'm better off where I am.
I got engaged soon after I joined the company...
When I was young, all I thought about was becoming a good wife.
I have no choice... do I?
And that's the only way I can protect Reina...
I've never been married, but it sounds hard, even for a normal family.
Dai, you're doing it all by yourself.
It's pretty amazing.
Nah, I haven't been able to do anything for her.
That's not true. Rin looks really happy.
Like when she's cooking for you.
And Kouki and his mom are doing their best alone too.
Reina and I will be fine.
It's always just you and Reina.
Did you talk to your husband about this?
He works overtime every night. We've never have a decent conversation.
That's why Reina and I will try our best.
Besides, I've been putting up with it for years now.
It'll work out.
As long as I ignore it, I should be able to survive.
That sounds really unhealthy...
It's just the opposite!
I'd be dead if I didn't do that.
You've gotten stronger, Haruko...
Mmm, I don't know about that...
After you give birth and raise a kid,
there are times when you need to be strong, right?
Especially when they're still babies...
I don't know what it's like with a baby, but...
And while you're keeping that up, for some reason...
you naturally become like this.
I really don't wanna be an old woman...
I didn't try to get stronger...
If I could, I'd be young forever...
I'm sorry, Dai.
Thank you.
We'll go home tomorrow.
I see...
What is "marriage"?
What does it mean to be a parent?
What's wrong?
It's your turn, Reina.
I knew it!
What?
Papa's car!
Papa's coming after he finishes his work.
He's never this early.
I'm positive it's Papa!
I'm not wrong!
It's not him! Reina!
Papa!
I was worried about you, Reina.
I was worried, too!
Sorry.
What? So if he wants to get off work early, he can, huh?
Hey, don't put it like that!
It's tough working for a company.
Hideyuki, you ass.
I apologize.
Haruko caused you so much trouble...
Oh, no, no... I didn't really...
I really don't know what to say...
I'm wearing the wrong clothes!
Thanks a lot, Dai.
Papa should've at least gotten our bags, right?
He's so inconsiderate.
I know! He's inconsirit!
If you ever feel like it, you can come back anytime.
Oh no... I've bothered you enough already.
No... That's not what I meant.
Rin is always saying that she wants to see Reina.
Thank you... Dai...
Mama! Mama!
Then can we come again on Sunday?
L-Listen, Reina...
When she was young, Haruko was such a crybaby.
Last night, she muttered that she wanted to stay young forever.
Well...
Next time you come, pack a little lighter.
I hate even looking at that bag.
Impossible!
Girls always have a heavy load to bear.
This is nothing.
Bye-bye!
I'll see you off!
A sunny early Sunday afternoon
Let's go somewhere today
It's the same road I'm used to traveling
But I can see it sparkling so bright
With the sun shining down its warmth
And you here by my side...
I'm already high, high, high
I feel like dashing out
Sing, la, la, la
My voice out to forever
I'm already high, high, high
Ride the dancing wind
Sing, la, la, la
My voice springs up
How about this one?
Yeah!
But maybe this one suits you more, Rin...
Here, what do you think?
Can I try this one on too?
Yeah, sure.
I'm thirsty!
She just has to try this one on...
Oh, this one's cute, isn't it?
Kouki and I are gonna go wander around...
Okay!
See, this one is really you!
Let's go.
You look so cute, Rin!
That good?
It tastes like summer!
I hear ya!